#### Contact

+56968289393 (Mobile) rivafelix@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ felixrivasproductdesigner (LinkedIn) felixrivasuxdesigner.github.io/ portfolio/ (Portfolio)

#### Top Skills

Organizational Culture
Artificial Intelligence for Business
Artificial Intelligence

#### Certifications

Python esencial

Multinational Communication in the Workplace

# Félix Rivas

UX/UI Designer | Project Management, CSR, NFTs | CEO @shapecreativestudio

Santiago, Santiago Metropolitan Region, Chile

# Summary

As the Chief Executive Officer of Shape Creative Studio Chile, a digital transformation company, I lead a team of talented professionals who design and develop innovative solutions for our clients. I have more than 15 years of experience in the design field, specializing in interface design and user experience for mobile and web applications. I also have knowledge in front-end technologies such as HTML, CSS, Sass, JavaScript, and React, as well as design tools such as Sketch, Photoshop, After Effects, InDesign, and Final Cut Pro.

My passion is to create attractive user experiences that improve the interaction of people with the designed products, using user-centered design principles and methods. I am also interested in exploring the influence of AI and NFTs on design, and how they can create new opportunities and challenges for designers. My long-term professional goals are to continue growing in my career and develop innovative projects that contribute to improving people's lives through design.

# Experience

Shape Creative Studio
Chief Executive Officer
February 2024 - Present (1 year 3 months)
Remote

#### **APLICA**

User Experience Designer
July 2024 - December 2024 (6 months)
Santiago, Santiago Metropolitan Region, Chile

Emergya Chile UX/UI Designer

July 2023 - January 2024 (7 months)

Santiago Metropolitan Region, Chile

Shape Creative Studio

Freelance UX/UI Designer

August 2022 - June 2023 (11 months)

Santiago, Santiago Metropolitan Region, Chile

In my role as a UX/UI designer, my main responsibility is to design and develop user interfaces that are intuitive, accessible, and visually appealing.

The Bridge Social

**UX** Designer

June 2022 - July 2022 (2 months)

Online

Create schemes and user flows that allow customers to easily shop and purchase products from our app. Design the app layout to be easy to use, visually appealing, and intuitive. Work closely with developers to ensure their designs are implemented correctly.

Nectia

**UX/UI** Designer

February 2022 - February 2022 (1 month)

Online

Design and build reusable, modular components that can be used across multiple applications.

Work closely with the product manager to understand the user needs and design solutions that meet those needs.

Create wireframes, prototypes, mockups and visual designs for web applications.

Mits

**UX/UI** Designer

March 2021 - January 2022 (11 months)

Santiago Metropolitan Area

Design and develop new features for internal web app

Work with product managers to determine vision for new features and improvements to existing features

Collaborate with product designers to determine visual style, layout, and usability of new features

Shape Creative Studio

#### **UX/UI** Designer

August 2020 - January 2021 (6 months)

Santiago, Santiago Metropolitan Region, Chile

#### Andain

Web Designer

September 2019 - June 2020 (10 months)

Santiago Metropolitan, Chile

#### Banesco Banco Universal

Web Design Especialist

March 2017 - January 2018 (11 months)

Caracas Area, Venezuela

#### Diario El Universal

Frontend Developer(UX/UI)

August 2012 - March 2017 (4 years 8 months)

Caracas

#### Adverweb

Diseñador Web

October 2011 - July 2012 (10 months)

Caracas

#### Grupo SMS

Web Designer, Diseñador Web

January 2010 - April 2011 (1 year 4 months)

Caracas

Design and development of RIA's prototypes under Flash Builder technology,

Web Portals (Joomla)

## Education

**IMF Smart Education** 

Master's degree, Project Management · (January 2024)

#### **Udemy Alumni**

Artificial Intelligence for Business (January 2023 - January 2023)

#### Crehana

Estrategia UX en las organizaciones (December 2022 - December 2022)

### Crehana

Diseño de interacción ágil para productos · (November 2022 - November 2022)

### Crehana

Storytelling: El arte de contar historias · (October 2022 - October 2022)